(Bernadette:)FYI, she's getting you
a watch for your birthday
(Bernadette:)with money she took
out of your wallet.
(Sheldon:)I don't mean to be rude
or discourteous,
(Sheldon:)but before we begin,
l'd just like to say
(Sheldon:)there is absolutely
no scientific evidence
(Sheldon:)to support clairvoyance of any kind.
(Sheldon:)Which means,
and again, no insult intended,
but you're a fraud...
(Sheldon:)...your profession is a swindle,
and your livelihood is dependent
on the gullibility of stupid people.
Again, no offense.
(Penny:)All right, Sheldon,
just ask your question.
(Sheldon:)Okay, I just did.
What was it?
(Penny:)Oh, for God's sake. Look, he's a
physicist who's trying to figure out
what his next Held
of study should be.
(Sheldon:)For your information, I was asking her
about the next Star Trek movie.
(Penny:)I'll be bored.